dontpkethebear.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy and Copyright Notice - Dontpokethebear.com

**This privacy policy sets out how this site[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.**

**We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, and then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.**

**[Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/) may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from February 10, 2013.**

**What we collect**

**We may collect the following information:**

**Name.**  
**Contact information including email address.**  
**Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests.**  
**Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers.**

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

**Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes).**

**User generated content**

**In these terms of use, “your user content” means material (including without limitation text, images, audio material, video material and audio-visual material) that you submit to our website, for whatever purpose.**

**Your user content must not be illegal or unlawful, must not infringe any third party’s legal rights, and must not be capable of giving rise to legal action whether against you or us or a third party (in each case under any applicable law).**

**Security**

**We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.**

**How we use cookies**

**A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.**

**We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.**

**Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.**

**You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.**

**Links to other websites**

**Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.**

**Controlling your personal information**

**You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways.**

**If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at kingkuno831@gmail.com**

**We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.**

**You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email us at kingkuno831@gmail.com**

**If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.**

**Website disclaimer**

**The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. The information is provided by[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/), and while we try to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.**

**Links to Other Websites**

**Through this website you are able to link to other websites which are not under the control of[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/). We have no control over the nature, content and availability of those sites. The inclusion of any links does not necessarily imply a recommendation or endorse the views expressed within them.**

**Every effort is made to keep the website up and running smoothly. However,[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/) takes no responsibility for, and will not be liable for, the website being temporarily unavailable due to technical issues beyond our control.**

**Google Ads**

**Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.**

**Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet. Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy found here and addressing them directly at[ http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) .**

**Questions or Concerns**

**Any information used or collected on this site is strictly for entertainment purposes only. We will not be liable or responsible for the misuse of third party sharing or any visitors of the site who choose to copy any material and use it for their own personal entertainment. If a response or reply is requested, we ask that a reasonable amount of time is given for us to comply with the request.**

**This website and its content is copyright of[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/)**

**Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following:**

**You may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only.**  
**You may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material.**  
**You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system.**

**©[ Dontpkethebear.com](http://dontpkethebear.com/) February 10, 2013. All rights reserved.**

### Comments

comments
